我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
被困在孤岛上5年以来
我只有一个目标...活下去
For 5 years,I was stranded on an
island with only one goal... survive.
Oliver Queen还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.
现在 我要完成我父亲的夙愿
Now I will fulfill my
father's dying wish...
根据他留给我的名单
除掉那些毒害我城市的人
to use the list of names he left me and
bring down those who are poisoning my city.
为了完成目标 我必须扮成别人
To do this,I must become someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must become something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...
- 妈妈
- 你怎么来了
- Mom?
- What are you doing here?
我觉得Sarah还活着
I believe Sarah's still alive.
其实你没有任何证据
You don't actually have any proof.
我有 她不像Sarah吗
I have proof. Doesn't
it look just like Sarah?
我确实发现了些东西
I did manage to find one thing.
我想退出
I want to get out.
我要你帮我杀了Malcolm Merlyn
Malcolm Merlyn. I want
you to kill him for me.
我们当中有叛徒
We have a traitor in our midst.
他大错特错了
He just made his last mistake.
John Nickels的律师今天对媒体
Lawyers for John Nickels
spoke to the press today.
声称很高兴地检拒绝了对最近
Nickels其中一幢楼起火的指控
They say they're pleased the D.A. declined from the recent fire in
to indict their client on charges stemming one of Nickel's buildings.
John Nickel是斯特林市
最有钱的房地产开发商之一
John Nickel is one of the wealthiest
real estate developers in Starling City.
同时也是最肮脏的
He's also one of the dirtiest.
昨晚起火的那幢楼吗
That building that
burnt down last night?
- 线路没按质量要求接
- 也许他不知道
- Wiring was not up to code.
- Maybe he didn't know that.
他可能也不知道过去三年
有七个人冻死在他的楼里
I guess he also didn't know about the in his other buildings
seven people who have frozen to death over the past three years.
是啊 他是真男人
Yeah,he's a real man of the people.
做不了多久了
Not for long.
地检无视此事 贫民都在林中空地
The D.A. ignores this,and
the police can't do anything
所以警察也无能为力
because all these slums are in
the Glades. So tonight,Felicity,
Felicity 今晚我们要划掉Nickel的名字
we cross Mr. Nickel's name off the list.
你同意吗
You ok with that?
完全同意
100 percent.
他出去了吗
He was just gone?
不 不是出去 是被绑架了
No! Not gone. Taken.
貌似Nickel还在别人的名单上啊
Looks like Nickel was on
somebody else's list,too.
昨晚那场火之后也不足为奇
After the fire last night,it's
not entirely surprising.
Felicity 我需要你帮我
查出所有Nickel的信息
Felicity,I need you to get me
everything that you can on Nickel.
关注他的租客
Focus on his tenants,
对他有投诉记录的人
and anyone who might have filed a
formal complaint against him,or...
还有在大火中有所失去的人
people that lost something in the fire.
那肯定有个单子 贫民窟的议员
Well,it's going to be some list. I
mean,slum lords aren't generally known
一般不会知道他们的人口 而且...
for their popularity. Plus...
什么
What?
没什么 你一过去就是一副
Nothing,it's just... you
went over there to be all,
"改邪归正吧 不然我就射死你"的样子
"grrr,stop being bad or I'll arrow you,"
现在却要救他
and now you want to rescue him.
我不喜欢危险的人逍遥法外
I don't like the idea that
somebody dangerous is out there.
其他人
Somebody else.
因为他们没我那么有自制力
Because typically... They don't
show my level of restraint.
所以Nickel是肯定要被灭的咯
So you're going to
cross Nickel off anyway?
不
No.
我要找那个其他人谈谈
I'm finding somebody else
who needs a talking to.
你还要出去吗 Oliver
You're going out there again,Oliver?
回家陪你家人吧 兄弟
Why don't you go home and
be with your family,man?
这是任务完成后的事情 Diggle
That's when the work is done,Diggle.
行 那我们出去吃晚饭
Ok,then I'll take you out to dinner.
我现在不饿
I'm not hungry.
我不是在问你
I'm not asking.
简单交易
Simple exchange.
你想办法让我们离开这座岛
我们就给你电路板
You get us a way off the island,and
we'll give you the circuit board
你的导弹发射器就能运作了
so that your missile
launcher isn't just furniture.
我看 你学会不少嘛 Queen先生
You've grown up quite a bit,Mr. Queen.
我能给你们一艘船
I'll give you that.
但我需要时间
I can get you a boat. But I need time.
给你一小时 Fyers
不然你就永远...干嘛
You got an hour,Fyers,and
then you're never... what?!
我们知道你可能需要
不止一小时才能搞到船
We understand it might take you
longer than an hour to get a boat.
你需要调度
What we mean is you need
to move with some dispatch.
Wilson 你还是指挥吗
Ah,Wilson,still in command there,eh?
你的小宠物是不是要夺权了
I thought your little pet
had staged a coup d'etat.
给我们搞到船
Just get us the damn boat.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 Rosemary 旖旎 Ducky
校对: AndreaQuinn
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十八集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 18
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
这会儿怎么停了
Now you want to stop?
你以为每户都有管家呀
Well,we don't all have butlers.
得自己去开门
You know,some of us actually
have to answer our own doors.
真讨厌
Oh,the horror.
你有点眼熟啊
You look familiar.
你上过电视什么的吗
Did I see you on TV or something?
也许吧 我是Thea Queen
Probably. I'm Thea Queen.
是哦
Yeah,right.
拿来了吗
Did you get it?
明晚
Tomorrow night.
Joe要在11点见到我们
Joe wants us there at 11 p.m.
他说要准时 Harper
He said to be on time,Harper.
明晚11点要干嘛
What's happening tomorrow at 11:00?
我只关注现在的事
You know,I'm actually kind of
focused on what's happening right now.
好啊
Oh,ok. Yeah.
不 Thea 别
No,no,Thea,don't!
你拿枪干什么
Why do you have a gun?
因为我不擅长用刀
Because I'm no good with knives.
是一家卖酒的店
Look,it's just a liquor store.
那人是变态 相信我 他该死
The guy's a creep.
Trust me,he deserves it.
我把子弹拿了 好点了吧
Look,if it'll make you feel
any better... I won't be armed.
当然 他不会知道的
But of course,the owner
won't know that,but...
我给了你份我哥俱乐部的工作
你有选择的 不用非得做罪犯
I got you a job at my brother's club. You
have choices. You don't have to be a criminal!
这不是钱的问题
I'm not talking about phone bills.
是我欠别人的
I owe people.
更有权势的人
People with much bigger guns than this.
在林中空地 这是唯一的解决办法
Look,here in the Glades,this is
pretty much the only solution.
不 这里很多人都活得正派
No,lots of people in the
Glades live honest lives.
显然你不是
Obviously not you.
你就是一废物
You're just a waste.
不 Thea Thea
No,Thea. Thea!
我要确保你安全回家
I'm going to make sure you get home ok.
不用麻烦了
Don't bother.
嘿 宝贝
Hey,honey.
给
There you go.
这是什么情况
Um,what's all this?
你要我从你妈的线索下手找Sarah
我打了几个电话
Well,you asked me to look into your
mother's leads on Sarah,so I made some calls.
看来你不止做了这些啊
It looks like you did
a lot more than that.
是啊 是你说我们得做的 Laurel
Well,yeah,but you're the one who
said we should do this,Laurel,
如果有一丝可能你妹妹还活着...
so,you know,if there's even
a chance that your sister is...
- 嗯 可是...
- 谢谢
- yeah,but...
- thank you.
宝贝 抱歉这里一团乱
Hi,sweetheart,I'm sorry about the mess.
Quentin 我刚和普吉岛领事馆通电话
Quentin,I just got off the phone
with the consulate in Phuket.
部长说会从他们的数据库里
调查Sarah的照片
The secretary there's going to run
Sarah's photo against their database,
看看是否有匹配
see if there's a match.
不错
That's good work.
怎么了
What?
我以为你是想帮妈妈接受一些事
Well,I guess I just thought deep down that
you were going to help mom... accept things.
你我都已接受的事
Things you and I accepted.
是的 但你不得不承认
Yeah,but... You got to admit.
这个女孩很像Sarah
This girl,she looks a lot like Sarah.
Sarah也有这样的帽子
斯特林市火箭队的图案
Sarah had that same cap.
The Starling City Rockets.
是你爸买给她的 记得吗
Your dad bought it for her,remember?
我记得
Yeah,I remember.
是有离奇的事发生
Stranger things have happened.
是啊 我看出来了
Yeah. I can see that.
比想象中饿呀
Hungrier than I thought.
等我吃完你要发表演讲吗
Are you waiting for me to finish
before giving me the lecture?
Oliver 这几周你扮演
帽衫侠的时间太多了
Oliver,you've been spending a lot of time
under that hood the last couple weeks.
保持状态
Keeps my ears warm.
这样做是为了避免纠纷吗
And you made this decision
to,um,avoid entanglements?
为了保护他们
For their protection.
和我亲近的人会受伤
The people who get close to me get hurt.
怎么了
What's the problem?
你觉得我失控了吗
Do you think I'm losing my grip?
不 正好相反 你看起来很冷静
No,it's just the
opposite,really. You seem calm.
冷静得可怕
Scary calm.
我知道Helena和McKenna的结局都不太好
I get that things didn't end
well with Helena,with McKenna...
Laurel 还有Sarah
With Laurel. With Sarah.
- 以后还会有人受伤
- 好吧 但你做什么了
- The list goes on.
- Yeah. But what do you do?
行侠仗义后回家
不停地重复 这不是生活
You hood up,you go home,you
repeat. It's not much of a life.
我现在的生活方式
Well,the life that I'm
leading for myself right now
容不得我过正常人的生活
doesn't leave much
room for an actual life.
而且我也不需要
And I don't need one.
给自己安排的人生
还真暗淡...孤独终老
That's a pretty bleak future you
plan on spending...with no one.
我习惯一个人了
I'm used to isolation.
这正是我担心的
And that is exactly what worries me.
你回家已经8个月了 Oliver
但我觉得你还没离开那座岛
You've been home for 8 months,Oliver,but
I don't think you left that island yet.
发生什么了
What the hell is going on?
找到Nickel了 打开我刚发你的链接
Found Nickel. Click the
link I just sent you.
每个IP手机都收到了
从林中空地发来的信息
This came up on every screen with an
I.P. address originating from the Glades.
如果你住在林中空地
你就知道这个人是谁
If you make the Glades your
home,you know who this man is.
John Nickel
John Nickel.
他拥有你的房屋
He owns your tenements.
管理你的贫民窟
Manages your slums.
给你提供漏雨的屋顶
Provides the leaking
roofs over your head.
水管里的霉菌 墙壁上的石棉
The mold in your pipes
and asbestos in your walls.
基本上 他赚的钱是建立在我们的苦难上
Basically,he makes
money off our suffering.
警方不想帮助我们
But the police aren't
interested in helping us.
他们也许让我们失望了 但我不会
They may have let us down,but I won't.
John 我给你个机会陈述
John,I want to give you the
chance to state your case.
你为什么不该受罚
Why shouldn't you be punished?
我知道我的建筑是豆腐渣工程
I knew there was bad
stuff in my buildings.
- 追踪他 Felicity
- 正在查
- Track him,Felicity.
- I'm looking.
没错 我挣了一点钱
Ok,yes,I made a little profit!
至少他们有个地方住
At least they had a place to live.
要是没有我 那样的人只能流落街头
Without me,people like that
would end up on the street.
"那样的人"
"People like that."
在他这样的人眼里 我们什么都不是
That's all we are to guys like this.
别动
Don't.
我宣布...你有罪
I find you... Guilty.
还有更多人要为他们犯下的罪付出代价
There are plenty more people who need
to answer for their crimes against us.
那么...下一个会是谁呢
So... Who's next?
发现什么了
Anything new?
这个家伙绝对不止连线这么简单
This guy's definitely got more
than a subscription to "Wired."
他的网站经过严格的加密保护
His website's protected by
some very serious encryption.
用那个空气磁铁 你说过它可以追踪...
Well,use that air magnet thing,you
said that it could trace...
Oliver 无意冒犯
我有对你的弓箭指手画脚吗
Oliver! No offense. Do I tell
you how to sharpen your arrows?
根据我在国安局的朋友
Spoke to my friend at the NSA.
网站编码与他们
正追踪的网络十字军相符
The website code matches a cyber
crusader who's been on their radar.
他以"救世主"的名义黑进了极端网站
He hacks into fringe sites
under the user name "The Savior."
国安局认为他曾是林中空地的居民
NSA believes he's a former
resident of the Glades.
- 曾是
- 一年前 他把自己弄得人家蒸发
- Former?
- Yeah,well,a year ago,he hacked himself right off the radar.
抹除了他的所有痕迹
He erased all traces of his existence.
一年前发生什么了
So what happened a year ago?
我们回来了
We're back.
和我一起的是
地方助理检察官Gavin Carnahan
I have with me assistant
district attorney Gavin Carnahan.
地方检察官的职责是逮捕坏人
Now,DAs are supposed
to go after bad guys.
但是这个人甚至懒得带他们去审训
But this one can't even be
bothered to bring them to trial.
就像在酒店杀了我妻子的那些人
Like the ones who killed
my wife in a bodega.
- Felicity...
- 在查
- I'm on it.
他们说没有足够的证据
They said there wasn't enough evidence.
你认为她在斯特林市的良好社区被杀
You think the evidence
would have turned up
证据会自己出现吗
if she'd been killed in one of
Starling City's nicer neighborhoods?
Emma Falk 悲痛的丈夫是Joseph Falk
能查到什么
Emma Falk. Grieving husband is
Joseph Falk. What do we have on him?
不多 42岁 曾是市政人员
Not much. 42,former city worker.
运输部的电脑技术员
Department of
transportation,computer technician,
妻子被杀后离职 就在去年的今天
left his job when she was
killed. One year ago today.
没有现在的电话和住址
No current phone,no current address.
Gavin 你是一个律师 你习惯申辩
Gavin,you're a lawyer.
You're used to making a case.
那么来吧
So go ahead.
我给你十分钟的时间
I'm going to give you ten minutes
来发表最后的声明
to deliver the closing
argument of your life.
- 快点
- 正在锁定他的无线信号
- Come on.
- I'm trying to get a lock on his wireless signal.
给你十分钟说服我不杀你
10 minutes to convince
me not to blow you away.
在医院的时候 Malcolm想让你做什么
What did Malcolm want
with you last night?
一个报复的目标
A target for reprisal.
他想要以牙还牙 他不会善罢甘休的
He wants justice,and he's not
going to stop until he gets it.
情况还不错
Besides,this is good.
我想你对"不错"的定义需要调整下
I think your definition of
good requires an adjustment.
不 他来找我 说明他还不知道
No,he came to me. Which
means he doesn't know
我们是想要谋杀他的人
that we're responsible for
the attempt on his life.
还不知道
Yet.
Malcolm 查到是谁
雇了三合会刺杀他的可能性有多大
What are the chances of Malcolm discovering
who paid the triad to assassinate him?
我很谨慎
I was very discreet.
我用海外账户通过我的空壳公司汇的钱
I wired the money through a shell
corporation I own,from an offshore account.
海外的 好的 很好
Offshore? Good. That's good.
我让Amanda去伦敦几周 以防万一
I'm sending Amanda to London for
a few weeks,just as a precaution.
也许你也应该安排一下你的家人
Perhaps you should do
the same for your family.
为了我的孩子我做什么都愿意 Frank
There's nothing I wouldn't do
to protect my children,Frank.
我能跟你聊聊吗
Hey,can I talk to you about something?
女人之间的谈话
Almost woman to woman.
我现在很忙
I'm really busy right now.
好吧
Ok.
Thea
Thea.
抱歉
Sorry.
怎么了
What's up?
我需要点建议
I could use some advice.
我正和一个"坏男孩"约会
I'm sort of dating this guy who would
definitely be described as a bad boy.
我想你跟很多这样的人约会过
And I figured,as someone who's
dated like a gajillion of them...
我没约会过那么多
I haven't dated a gajillion.
好吧 或许有
All right,guilty as charged.
要听我的意见吗 躲得远远的
You want my advice? Run.
有多远离多远
As fast as you possibly can.
是 那也是我的第一反应 但...
Yeah. See,that was my
first instinct,too,but...
Laurel 2号线 中国大使馆
Laurel? The Chinese
embassy's on line two.
我转接过来了
I'm transferring him over.
中国大使馆
Chinese embassy?
我正忙的一个案子
It's just this case that I'm working on.
过会我们接着聊
But we are definitely continuing
this conversation later.
多谢回电
Thank you so much for
getting back to me.
我正在找我发给你照片上的女子
I'm trying to track down a woman
in the photo that I emailed you.
你找到了
You did.
真的吗
Really?
你确定她现在就在美国吗
And you're sure that
she's in the states now?
你不会刚好有她的联系地址吧
Do you happen to have an address on her?
- 找到他了
- 关了他的信号
- I got him!
- Shut it down.
不行 他有防火墙保护无线信号
Can't. He has a firewall
protecting his wireless signal.
但他在23街和米拉街之间有个IPX
But he's working off an IPX
located at 23rd and Mira.
- 你要乔装一下吗
- 现在是大白天
- You want to hood up?
- The middle of the day!
听着 听着 听我说
Look! Listen. Listen to me. Ok.
我的桌上现在有53个案子
I have 53 cases on my desk right now.
我没有时间处理每个案子
I don't always have time
to take on every case!
Carnahan怎么样了
How's Carnahan?
不是很有说服力
Not making a very persuasive argument.
我快到了
I'm almost there.
- 发现什么了
- 我刚到第一层
- See anything?
- I'm only on the first floor.
还有6层
Just six more to go.
没有那么多资源 我努力了
There aren't resources. I tried.
- 天哪 对不起
- Oliver 快点
- Oh,my God! I'm sorry!
- Oliver,hurry.
找不到他
Can't find him!
- 他不在这 Felicity
- 什么
- He's not here,Felicity!
- What?!
我找了每层的每间屋子
I searched every office on every floor!
他不在这 是这里吗
He's not here. Is this the right place?
- 你确定吗
- 是 我...
- Are you sure?
- Yeah,I...
- 噢 见鬼
- 什么
- Oh,crap.
- What?
这怎么可能 怎么会 他...
How is this possible?!
This can't happen! He's...
- 跟我说
- 等等
- Talk to me!
- Wait.
他移动了 就在你的北边 大洋和格兰街
He moved. Just north
of you. Ocean and Grand.
这就去
On my way!
我只处理我觉得我可以...
I took on cases that were...that
I thought that I could...
- 赢的案子
- 对
- Win.
- Yes.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
Gavin Carnahan 我宣布
你愧对于林中空地的居民
Gavin Carnahan,I find you guilty
of crimes against the Glades.
不要 不要
Don't do this! Don't do this!
我判你死刑
And I sentence you to death.
我赶到了 Felicity 这儿是块空地
I'm at Ocean and Grand,Felicity.
That's just a vacant lot.
怎么可能 这不应该 他...
How is this possible?
This can't happen. He...
查出正确地址 快
Find the right address,now!
Oliver 没用了 Carnahan死了
Oliver,it's over,Carnahan is dead.
Diggle呢
Where's Diggle?
我大声对他说
I asked him to leave me alone.
我要静一静
In my loud voice.
这不是你的错
This wasn't your fault.
本该由我来找到Carnahan
I was the one who was
supposed to find Carnahan,
但正是我给了你假地址
and I was the one who sent
you that bogus location.
我从未目睹过谁死去
I've never seen anybody die.
这是难免的 我们做的事
This is the thing with what we do.
有时会失败
Sometimes we lose.
或许单身更好
Maybe it is better being alone.
现在我没跟谁约会
I'm not seeing anyone currently,but...
否则我真不知 该怎么跟他说今天的事
If I were,I don't know how
I'd tell him about today.
先生们 欢迎啊
Gentlemen. Welcome.
很高兴我们能达成共识
So happy we were able
to reach an accord.
还跟我闲聊呢
Oh,good. Small talk.
继续聊吗
Are we going to get on with this?
好 说正题吧
As you wish. Straight to business.
电路板在哪儿
The circuit board. Where is it?
安全的地方
Somewhere safe.
带我们上船 就告诉你它藏哪儿了
So get us to the boat and then
we'll tell you where it is.
你们最好别骗我
And of course you'll be
honest about its location.
我可不想说实话
Well,I wouldn't be.
可这哥们执着于讲原则 守诚信
But this one's got some strange hang
up about principles and integrity.
我想也是
I always imagined as much.
因此我想提个相反的建议
Which is why I'd like to
make a counter proposal.
带上来
Men!
不
No!
把电路板给我 否则我杀了姚飞的女儿
You will deliver back to me the circuit
board,or I will kill Yao Fei's daughter.
所以我不能走了
So I wouldn't leave.
你这么有原则的人 我不相信你会
I can't imagine you want the death of
an innocent young woman on your hands.
目睹一个年轻女孩因你而死
Not with your... Principles.
你收集的关于Sarah的证据
我想自己做些调查
I wanted to do some research on my own into
the evidence that you gathered on Sarah.
所以我拜托了一个大学同学
他在中国大使馆工作
So I called my friend from law school
who works at the Chinese embassy,and...
照片上的女孩
The photo of the girl.
我找到她了
I found her.
抱歉 能借用下你的手机吗
I'm sorry. Can I...
can I borrow your phone?
我答应了未婚夫 晚饭前打给他
但我手机没电了
I promised my fianée that I'd call
him before dinner. My phone's dead.
Jen 他们是我父母
Jen,these are my parents.
很高兴认识你们
Hi. Nice to meet you.
我也是
Yeah,you,too.
我告诉Jen 这张照片
突然出现在我负责的案子里
I just told Jen about this photograph that
popped up in this case that I'm working on.
照片上的人是你吗
Is that you in the picture?
对 我在那个中国海岛上呆了6个月
Yeah. I spent six months on an
island off the coast of China.
照片是在一个叫Zhengjiu的渔村里拍的
That was taken in a small
fishing village called Zhengjiu.
- 中文意思是...
- 拯救
- It's Mandarin for...
- Salvation.
你没事吧 Lance夫人
Are you all right,Mrs. Lance?
没事 只是 你长得很像我认识的一个人
Yes,I... it's just,uh,you look
like someone I used to know.
我正等着呢
I was waiting for this.
等什么
Waiting for what?
你的长篇大论 "你可以改变"
"我会认识到真正的你"
The whole "You can change,I
can see the real you" speech.
看看这儿 Thea
Look around,Thea.
这就是我的栖身之所
This is home sweet home for me.
要嘛挨饿 要嘛就干违法的事
能活到21岁就算走运了
You either starve or you do things that
mean you're lucky enough to make it to 21.
我不能接受那些
I can't accept that.
不 你不能接受我
No. You can't accept me.
- Roy Harper
- 我就是
Roy Harper?
以下是林中空地绑架案的进一步报道
More on the story out of the Glades.
绑匪又劫持一人 并在网上直播
The kidnapper seems to have another victim
and is broadcasting the feed to his website.
观众请注意 这是实况直播
我们也不知道接下来会看到什么
A warning to viewers,this is live footage,so
we're not sure what we're about to see.
来认识下Roy Harper
Meet Roy Harper.
因盗窃 抢劫 重伤他人罪被捕
Arrests for larceny and
robbery,aggravated assault.
他还没被绳之以法
And yet you're out on the street.
林中空地另一个逍遥法外的小子
就像杀死我妻子那人一样
Another gangbanger in the Glades running
free,like the ones who killed my wife.
我也来自林中空地
I'm grew up in the Glades,too.
但我没变成罪犯
And it didn't turn me into a criminal.
我认识那孩子
I know that kid.
- 怎么认识的
- Tommy
- How?
- Tommy!
上帝啊 不
Oh,God,no.
我不知还能去哪儿
I didn't know where else to go.
- 你认识他吗
- Roy是我的朋友
- You know him?
- Roy,he's my friend.
我们在吵架
突然冲出来一个家伙袭击了我们
And we were in a fight and some guy
came out of nowhere and just attacked us!
他不该死
He doesn't deserve to die!
我保证 他会没事的
I promise you,he's going to be ok.
你跟Tommy呆在这儿 好吗
You stay here with Tommy,all right?
- 喂
- Moira 我是Malcolm
- Hello?
- Moira,it's Malcolm.
我刚得知 中国黑帮的一个头儿被抓了
I've learned a high ranking member
of the Triad was just arrested.
我该跟他谈谈
Well,I should have a word with him.
我已经跟他谈了
他同意去查出是谁为了减刑
I already have. He's agreed to
find out who hired his organization
雇了他的组织来杀我
to assassinate me in return
for a reduced prison sentence.
今晚我们应该就会知道是谁想杀我
By tonight,we should know the name,or
names,of the people who tried to kill me.
很好
Good.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
照片上的人不是Sarah
So it's not Sarah in the photo.
但她肯定没死 Quentin
But she's still out there,Quentin.
我要去找她
And I'm going to find her.
我知道 你俩现在已经不抱希望了
Look,I understand now that neither of you
have the stomach to continue looking for her.
没关系
And that's fine.
很抱歉 我把你们扯进来
I'm sorry I involved you both.
如果能换她一命
我下地狱都可以 但那行不通
You know that I would cross to hell
and back to bring her home,but I can't!
她已经不在了 Di
'Cause she's gone,Di.
不
No.
你得放手了
You got to let go of this now.
不 我不能
No! I can't!
我也不会
I won't!
你怎么知道Sarah上船时带着帽子
How did you know Sarah had her hat
with her when she went on the boat?
你确信照片上的人是Sarah
You were so sure that the
girl in the photo was Sarah.
不是因为她是美国人
而是因为那顶帽子
Not because she was
American,but because of her hat.
爸爸买给她的那顶斯特林火箭帽子
Her Starling City Rockets
hat that dad bought her.
妈
Mom.
你怎么知道她带着那顶帽子
跟Oliver上船的
How did you know she took her hat with
her on "the Queen's Gambit" with Oliver?
因为我看见了
I saw her.
什么意思
What do you mean?
那天我回来早了 就看见她了
I came home early
that day,and I saw her.
Sarah
Sarah.
我看见她把帽子放进包里
I saw her put the hat in a bag.
她在收拾行李
She was packing.
你知道她要跟他走
You knew she was going with him?
我叫她别那样做 别那样对你 Laurel
I told her not to... I told her
not to do this,not to you,Laurel.
可她说她陷入爱河 要追随心之所属
But she said she was in love
and she had to follow her heart,
即使大家都觉得她错了
even if nobody else
thought it was right.
就像我告诉过她 我也曾那样过
Just like I told her... Just
like I told her I once did.
所以 我让她走了
So... I let her go.
是我害死她的
I killed her.
我害死了自己的女儿
I... I killed my daughter.
我害死了她
I killed her.
对不起 Quentin
I'm so sorry,Quentin.
我害死了我的孩子
I killed our baby.
有线索了吗
Anything?
我把视频都看了一遍
I've been going through
all the video we got,
想找出蛛丝马迹 透露出他们的所在地
trying to see if there's anything
that'll tell us where this guy is.
一无所获 除了一个声音
I got nothing,except a sound.
隐含在背景杂音中 比较有节奏
Buried in the ambient
noise. Almost rhythmic.
我把它分离出来了
Here,I've isolated it.
是什么声音
What is that?
像是轿车碾过行车线标记
Sounds like a car
driving over lane markers.
比轿车大多了
It's bigger than a car.
- 比轿车大 巴士吗
- 等等 我知道
- Bigger than a car. What,a bus?
- Uh... wait,I know this.
我知道了
I know it.
加油 伙计们
Come on! Guys!
Felicity 给我看看绑架地点的地图
我们看见信号的那地方
Felicity,show me a map. Sights of the
abductions on where we've seen the signal so far.
那儿 就是那儿
Right there,right there.
第23大道和Mira大道
23rd and Mira.
Locksley街和Adams街
Locksley and Adams.
威尔斯街 国家创研会旁
Wells street down by CNRI.
- 这都是地铁站啊
- 斯特林城没有地铁
- Those are all subway stops!
- Starling City doesn't have a subway.
对 但以前有
小时候我爸常带我去看火箭队比赛
No,but they used to. When I was a kid,my
dad used to take me down to the Rockets game.
乘地铁去 我靠在窗边14分钟
By subway. For 14 minutes,I'd
lean against the window,
感受地铁飞驰的韵律
feeling the rhythm of the train moving.
他就是这么干的
That's how he did it.
他在23号和Mira 但在地下
He was at 23rd and
Mira,but he was underground.
他曾为交通部工作
He used to work for the
department of transportation,
所以他清楚所有的老地铁站
so that's why he knows
all the old subway stops.
所以我没法追踪信号
That's why I couldn't trace the signal.
他在移动 在地铁里
He was moving. He was in a subway car.
他现在在哪
Where is he now?
他在老的跨城线上
He's on the old cross town line.
要是他沿这条线走
15分钟后到达春天街道站
If he continues on this route,he'll be
at the Spring Street stop in 15 minutes.
放了那女孩
Let the girl go.
不做笔交易吗
No deal?
很好 杀了她
Very well. Kill her.
不
No!
这可没想到
That was unexpected.
开枪
Fire!
快来
Come on! Come on!
带她去安全的地方 快
Get her to safety! Now!
我只会拖累你们 快走
I'll only slow you down. Go!
快走 你得走了
Just go! You've got to go!
走吧
Go! Go!
- 来了
- 我给你10分钟叙述理由 Roy
- It's happening.
- I'll give you 10 minutes to state your case,Roy.
告诉我们
So tell us.
为什么你还活着
Why do you get to live?
我不该活着的
I shouldn't.
杀了我吧
Just do it.
杀了我
Kill me.
下手吧 杀了我
Just go on! Kill me!
你不在乎你是死是活吗
You really don't care
if you live or die?
没人会想我的
No one's going to miss me.
我就是个废物
I'm just a waste.
那我们达成一致了
Then we agree on something.
这世界没你会更好
This world would be better
off without you in it.
好像没影像了
We seem to have lost the feed.
我们会追踪此事
有任何进展将继续报道
We will stay on this story and keep
you up to date on any developments.
放了那孩子
Let the kid go.
你杀了他 便永不得悔改的机会
You kill this kid,you'll never
get an opportunity to change!
你可以再给他个机会
You can give him a second chance.
只有我们能救这座城市
We're the only ones
who can save this city.
不能现在停止
We can't stop now.
我们不一样
We're not the same!
你我都为这座城市杀了人
You've killed people
for this city,so have I.
咱俩有何区别
What's the difference
between you and me?
Emma没得到第二次机会
Emma never got her second chance.
你不知道这有多孤单
You have no idea how lonely it is.
Joseph
Joseph.
Joseph!
我理解你的孤独
I understand being alone.
但这不是你冷血杀人的理由
But it doesn't give you the right
to kill people in cold blood.
这是他应得的
He deserves it.
他和那些杀了她的少年犯并无两样
Just like the gangbangers who gunned
her down,he's no different than them.
我现在要杀了他
And now I get to gun him down.
别这么做
Don't do it!
我要去机场了
Got to get going to the airport.
坐红眼航班去中心城
That red eye to Central City.
我马上就能到家了
I should be home in a flash.
妈
Mom.
给我打打电话
Call me some time.
我喜欢这样
I'd really like that.
你愿意吗
You would?
当然
Of course I would.
你是我妈
You're my mother.
我很爱你
I love you so much.
我也爱你
I love you,too.
Roy Harper
向左转
a**
我以为你要死了
I thought you were going to die.
我也以为
That makes two of us.
我可能看起来很糟
I probably look like a mess.
我要去洗手间梳洗一番
I'm going to go to the
bathroom and freshen way,way up.
好
Ok.
Ollie
Ollie?
我听说Thea的朋友没事
I heard Thea's friend was ok.
完好解决了
Yeah. That worked out ok.
这个Roy不只是朋友 对不
This Roy... is more than
just a friend,isn't he?
坏男孩啊
Bad boys.
次次吸引你
Hook you every time.
我觉得Tommy今晚回家了
Oh,I think,uh,Tommy actually
went home for the night.
你还好吗
You all right?
看起来你不太好
You seem like you're
something other than all right.
我妈 这周来镇上 她觉得...
My mom,she showed up in town
this week and she's been...
什么
What?
她觉得Sarah还活着
She had this crazy idea
that Sarah was still alive.
她坚信自己是对的
弄得我也快要相信了
She was so sure of it that she
kind of had me believing it,also.
但是Sarah不在了
But Sarah's gone.
是啊
Yeah.
真不敢相信我就这么信了
I can't believe she
sucked me in like that.
- 你想她
- 我想她们
- You miss her.
- I miss them both.
谢谢你听我说这些
Thanks for listening.
没事
Of course.
Laurel
Laurel.
要不要一起吃晚饭...
或者喝杯咖啡 都行
Want to have dinner,or...
coffee,I don't know.
怎么了
Why?
我不想再这么孤单了
I don't want to be on an island anymore.
- 晚安
- Good night.
Slade
Slade?
电路板没了
Circuit board's gone.
靠 Fyers耍咱们
Damn. Fyers played us.
他在咱们耍咱的时候
他的人在树丛里找电路板
While he was screwing us around,his
men were combing the woods for it.
现在他的导弹发射器可以运转了
Now his missile launcher
is fully operational.
他永远不会
让咱们离开这座岛了 我懂了
And he was never going to let
us off the island,I get it!
他当然不会帮你
Of course he wasn't going to help you.
他不能冒着让你们警告大陆
关于他的计划的险救你们
He couldn't chance you warning
the mainland what he has planned.
- 她会说英语
- 告诉你吧
- She speaks English.
- Yeah,well,guess what.
我俩根本不知道他的计划是什么
Neither one of us have any
idea what his plans are.
我知道
I do.
谢谢你能来 Frank
Thank you for coming,Frank.
这样见面很危险 Moira
Meeting like this is dangerous,Moira.
- 尤其是现在
- 我知道
- Particularly now.
- Yes,I know.
- Malcolm知道咱们见面
- 什么
- Malcolm knows.
- What?
我一直在考虑我发现的事情
I had no choice but to turn
over what I've discovered.
关于电子转账的证据
你付的钱去暗杀Triad
The evidence of the wire transfer; the money
that you paid the Triad to assassinate him.
那钱...Moira
The money I... Moira!
Merlyn先生 感谢你的忠诚
Mr. Merlyn thanks you for your loyalty.
做的很好
You've done well.
Chen的家人会和他有相同的下场
Now Chen's family will share his fate.
Chen背叛了我们 但他的女儿没有
Chen betrayed us,but
his daughter didn't.
告诉Merlyn先生 我想让他的女儿活着
Tell Mr. Merlyn I want her to live.
Amanda在林中空地差点没了命
现在她爸爸已经死了
Amanda nearly lost her life in the
Glades,now she's lost her father.
我觉得她受的罪够多了
I think she's suffered enough.
我们必须要做出警告
We must send a message.
已经警告过了
We have.
- 很好
- 谢谢
- Very well.
- Thank you...
- Thea上楼了
- 我看到了
- Thea's friend is upstairs.
- I saw.
你可能看到他们见面很开心
You probably saw that they were
very happy to see each other,
你懂我的意思吧
if you know what I mean.
可能你不想谈
毕竟是你的宝贝妹妹
Which you probably don't want to talk
about,because she's your baby sister.
你还好吗
You ok?
快好了
I'm getting there.
谢谢
Thank you.
对了
By the way.
如果你想找人聊聊你的生活
可以跟我说
If you ever need to tell someone
about your day... You can tell me.
那是什么
What's that?
Felicity找出的
是一张废弃的老地铁线路图
Felicity pulled it up. It's an old
map of a decommissioned subway line.
在城市低租地区地下运行
Runs underneath the low
rent district of the city.
我见过这张地图
I've seen that map before.
一直都就在我们眼前
It was right in front of
our faces the entire time.
我爸 另外一个弓箭手 那个担保
不管是什么的计划
My father,the other archer,the
undertaking,whatever the plan is.
都和林中空地有关
It's all connected to the Glades.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 Rosemary 旖旎 Ducky
校对: AndreaQuinn
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十八集 完
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 18
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo